hey guys this looks like a fun one we
want to solve for x and this is kind of
a staggered fraction if you want to try
it on your own pause it right now cuz
I'm going to solve it in three 2 1 the
way this is staggered you could say is
ambiguous but I'm pretty sure it's meant
to be a fraction on either side where
these are on top and these are on bottom
so let's change this four into a 4 over
one and let's change this 69 into a 69
over one so now it's a little bit less
ambiguous it's going to be this / this
equals this / this let's see if we can
make a animation for that it'll be 4
piun / 691 = 41 / x 69 dividing
fractions can be a little bit tricky but
there's a cool shortcut you can leave
the first fraction alone so we can copy
down the 4 over pi and the 4 over1 then
you change the divide into a multiply
and then you flip the second fraction so
69 over 1 becomes 1 over 69 and X over
69 becomes 69x and now multiplying
fractions is a lot easier you just
multiply across on top and on bottom and
now we can just clean things up 4 * 1 is
equal to 4 and < * 69 is 69 piun 4 * 69
is equal to 276 and 1 * X is just X now
we have a fraction equals a fraction we
can solve this by cross multiplying we
can do 4 * x = 4x and that's equal to 69
piun * 276 that's 19,44 piun and then we
can divide both sides by 4 and we get X
is equal to
4761 pi and this is the answer to the
question let's put a box around it and
that's approximately equal to
14957 one2 and let's put a box around
that too how exciting